http://www.heritageparkzoo.org/index.php/component/content/article/2-uncategorised/68-privacy-policy

Friday, 11 December 2020
HomeAbout UsOur Animals
Large MammalsSmall MammalsHoofstockBirdsReptilesInvertebratesConservation
Our ProjectsOur Rescued AnimalsEducation
Zoo CampsCoati CampBecome a DocentZooTeen ProgramPrograms / Outreach / ToursTeacher ResourcesEducation AnimalsFun FactsHelpful LinksEventsSip and PaintBreakfast With the AnimalsBehind-the-Scenes Photo TourZoo By MoonlightTaste of the WildBoo at the ZooWildlights & Holiday EventsSanta with the AnimalsDollar DaysSupportMembershipAdopt-an-AnimalSponsorshipsBusiness MembershipsMonetary DonationsIn-Kind DonationsVolunteerFry's Community RewardsShop Amazon Smile!Visiting
Contact & LocationHours, Admission & Sanctuary MapGroup Rentals & WeddingsKeeper for a Day & Junior KeeperPhotography Tours
The Prescott Animal Park Association D.B.A. Heritage Park Zoological Sanctuary, respects the privacy of our visitors, members, and donors. The purpose of this statement is to define our policy with regard to the collection and use of personally identifiable information via our website, www.heritageparkzoo.org.
Information Collected:
This website collects two kinds of information: anonymous information and personally identifiable information.
Anonymous information does not indentify specific individuals and is automatically transmitted by your browser.  This information can consist of: the URL (Uniform Resource Locator or address) of the web page your previously visited; the domain names and/or IP addresses of the computer you are using; and your browser software and operating system.  This information is used to monitor site usage and traffic patterns of our customers in order to improve our website.  This information is always devoid of any personally identifying information.
Personally Identifiable Information could include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and payment information.  By sending us an email e-mail or filling out an online form, you are sending us personal information.  We store this information in order to respond to or process your request.  We may use your information to send you futher information about our organization.  You may always opt-out of future mailings.
If you are purchasing a membership, making a donation, signing up for a fee-based event or program, or making a similar financial transaction through www.heritageparkzoo.org, we need to know your name, e-mail address, billing and shipping address, and payment information in order to process and fulfill your order.  All personal informatio we receive is kept secure.
Sharing Information:
Personal information obtained through the website will not be sold or given to third parties for marketing purposes.
Links:
Our website contains to websites maintained by other oarganizations.  Once you access an individual document on another website, you are subject to the provacy policy of the website containing that document.
Use of Text and Images:
Anyone wishing to publish information found on our website must send a request to
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
.
On Zoo Grounds and Commercial Photography:
Heritage Park Zoological Sanctuary reserves the right to photograph, videotape, or film our visitors, on Sanctuary grounds, for promotional purposes.  The commerical use of photographs, video, and film taken during your visit is strictly prohibited without the written consent of Heritage Park Zoological Sanctuary.
Contact Us:
If you have any questions regarding the website or this policy, please contact
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
